<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!DOCTYPE xml [
  <!ENTITY nbsp "&#160;"> 
  <!ENTITY lt   "&#60;"> 
  <!ENTITY gt   "&#62;">
  <!ENTITY sl   "&#47;">
]>

<xmlAnswer>




 <record>
       <attribute name="title">Analysis tools: Enrichment</attribute>
       <attribute name="image">images/choose_analysis_highlighted_550px.jpg</attribute>
       <attribute name="body">
<![CDATA[After running a search or strategy that returns genes, you can analyze the results to 
find statistically enriched Gene Ontology annotations, Metabolic Pathway annotations or 
words in the gene product descriptions. Click the blue Analyze Results button to run an enrichment
analysis on the gene result highlighted in yellow.<br><br> ]]>
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="tip">
 <![CDATA[
you can run an analysis on a gene result ? 
<br>Click on the blue button <img style='position:relative;top:5px' data-assets-src='wdk/images/strathelp/blueButton.png'> to select an analysis tool.
]]>
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="showTipAsDidYouKnow">true</attribute>
   </record>


 <record>
       <attribute name="title">Genome Browser: design PCR</attribute>
       <attribute name="image">images/GBrowseDesignPrimers_550px.jpg</attribute>
       <attribute name="body"><![CDATA[
       1. Direct the Genome Browser to the genomic location that you want to amplify. <br>
       2. Choose <b>Design Primers</b> from the drop down menu and click GO.  <br>
       3. The Primer Design application opens in a new 
       window where you can highlight the region you want to amplify, set your primer 
       parameters and click <b>Design Primers</b>.<br><br>
       
      ]]>

       </attribute>
       <attribute name="tip">
 <![CDATA[
 you can use the Genome Browser to design PCR primers ?
]]>
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="showTipAsDidYouKnow">true</attribute>
   </record>


<record>
       <attribute name="title">Genome Browser: bookmark configurations</attribute>
       <attribute name="image">images/Bookmark_550px.jpg</attribute>
       <attribute name="body"><![CDATA[
       Use the <b>Select Tracks</b> tab of the Genome Browser to turn on the data tracks that you want to view. 
       The Browser is automatically updated with the tracks you choose. To bookmark the view, choose 
       <b>Generate URL</b> from the <b>File</b> dropdown menu.  Then, using your internet browser, bookmark the 
       updated URL.  Use this bookmark to return to the GBrowse view or to share the view with 
       colleagues when discussing the data. <br><br>
       ]]>

       </attribute>
       <attribute name="tip">
 <![CDATA[
you can configure the Genome Browser to display specific data tracks ?
<br>(eg: proteomics or mRNAseq data from selected experiments)
<br>and you may also bookmark your favorite configurations for future use.
]]>
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="showTipAsDidYouKnow">true</attribute>
   </record>

<!-- 
<record>
       <attribute name="title">DNA motifs: identify genes in vicinity</attribute>
       <attribute name="image"></attribute>
       <attribute name="body">

       </attribute>
       <attribute name="tip">
 <![CDATA[
you can search for specific DNA motifs in the genome ?
<br>Also you may identify genes in the vicinity of these motifs.
]]>
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="showTipAsDidYouKnow">true</attribute>
   </record>
 -->

   <record>
       <attribute name="title">Add Step</attribute>
       <attribute name="image">wdk/images/strathelp/addstep.png</attribute>
       <attribute name="body">
Running a search places you in the Search Strategy system.  Your search is the first "step" of a new strategy.  To refine your result set, add steps to the strategy as needed.
Click the Add Step button to add a step.  You will be prompted to choose a search.  Next you will be prompted to combine the new search with the previous results (using intersect, union or minus).  The new results reflect this combination.
We hope strategies help you get the most from the data!
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="tip">
 <![CDATA[
you can click Add Step to add a step to your strategy ?
]]>
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="showTipAsDidYouKnow">true</attribute>
   </record>

   <record>
       <attribute name="title">View prior steps</attribute>
       <attribute name="image">wdk/images/strathelp/viewresults.png</attribute>
       <attribute name="body">
To view the results of a prior search or combination, click on a step box.
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="tip">
 <![CDATA[
you can see results of a previous step by clicking on its box ?
]]>
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="showTipAsDidYouKnow">true</attribute>
   </record>

   <record>
       <attribute name="title">Step actions menu</attribute>
       <attribute name="image">wdk/images/strathelp/adjuststep.png</attribute>
       <attribute name="body">
For a menu of actions/properties for a step's search click on the "Edit" icon near the step box.
For a menu of actions/properties for how it is combined with the prior step, click on the "Edit" icon near the Venn diagram.
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="tip">
 <![CDATA[
you can get a menu of step actions by clicking on the "Edit" icon ?
]]>
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="showTipAsDidYouKnow">true</attribute>
   </record>

   <record>
       <attribute name="title">Branched (nested) strategy</attribute>
       <attribute name="image">wdk/images/strathelp/nestedstep.png</attribute>
       <attribute name="body">
Simple strategies are linear.  More advanced strategies include branches.  (For example one step may need to union two searches.)  The trick is to "nest" a strategy within a step.
Click the "Edit" icon to get a menu.  Choose "Make Nested Strategy."  Now that step appears expanded in a panel below.  All steps added to that panel will be nested into the step in the panel above.  The whole nested strategy acts as a single step in the parent strategy.
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="tip">
 <![CDATA[
you can branch a strategy ?
<br>Choose "Make Nested Strategy" in the step actions menu.
]]>
       </attribute>
       <attribute name="showTipAsDidYouKnow">true</attribute>
   </record>

</xmlAnswer>
